A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Penitentiary, 1796-1991 (bulk 1906-1970)
Library of Virginia
- Series V. State Convict Road Force, 1904-1965 (bulk 1906-1949)., Extent: 31.78 cubic feet of records and 50 volumes. (Box 573-659., Volume 162-203, 222, 255, 268-269, 272-274 and 287.)
  - Series V. Subseries C. Correspondence, 1910, 1912, 1919-1930, 1933-1941. (Box 629-640.)
    - Files of E.J. Marrin, Chief Clerk and/or Assistant Superintendent L.H. Jones, 1926-1930
      - Camp 8, 1926-1930 (Sgt. J.E. Vines and Van Snellings). (Box 630, Folder 8)
      - Camp 9, 1926-1930 (Sgt. L.S. Reames). (Box 631, Folder 1)
      - Camp 10, 1926-1930 (Sgt. C.A. Coleman). (Box 631, Folder 2)
      - Camp 11, 1926-1929 (Sgt. F.B. Bishop). (Box 631, Folder 3)
      - Camp 12, 1926-1930 (Sgt. Van Snellings and J.E. Vines). (Box 631, Folder 4)
      - Camp 14, 1926-1930 (Sgt. R.E. Jennell). (Box 631, Folder 5)
      - Camp 15, 1928-1930 (Sgt. W.W. Harvey). (Box 631, Folder 6)
      - Camp 16, 1926-1930 (Sgt. Mont Johnston and J.L. Bishop). (Box 631, Folder 7)
      - Camp 16, 1922-1926 (Sgt. J.L. Bishop and C.D. Fugate). (Box 631, Folder 8)
      - Camp 20, 1927-1929 (Sgt. G.W. Earman). (Box 632, Folder 1)
      - Camp 21, 1926-1930 (Sgt. R.H. Blevins). (Box 632, Folder 2)
      - Camp 24, 1926-1930 (Sgt. W.W. Higginbotham). (Box 632, Folder 3)
      - Camp 29, 1926-1930 (Sgt. C.G. Landes and W.S. Brent). (Box 632, Folder 4)
      - Camp 30, 1926-1930 (Sgt. L.E. Clouse). (Box 632, Folder 5)
      - Camp 31, 1926-1930 (Sgt. A.M. Johnston and W.B. Sirman). (Box 632, Folder 6)
      - Camp 32, 1926-1930 (Sgt. W.W. Harvey and L.M. Royster). (Box 633, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Supply Purchases, etc., 1926-1928. (Box 633, Folder 2)
      - State Highway Department, Camp Maintenance Costs, 1925-1928 (part one). (Box 633, Folder 3)
      - State Highway Department, Camp Maintenance Costs, 1925-1928 (part two). (Box 633, Folder 4)
      - L.H. Jones, Assistant Superintendent, State Convict Road Force, Personal Correspondence, 1924-1930 (part one). (Box 633, Folder 5)
      - L.H. Jones, Assistant Superintendent, State Convict Road Force, Personal Correspondence, 1924-1930 (part two). (Box 633, Folder 6)
      - L.H. Jones, Assistant Superintendent, State Convict Road Force, Personal Correspondence, 1924-1930 (part three). (Box 634, Folder 1)
      - L.H. Jones, Assistant Superintendent, State Convict Road Force, Personal Correspondence, 1924-1930 (part four). (Box 634, Folder 2)
      - Telegrams, 1929-1930 (part one). (Box 634, Folder 3)
      - Telegrams, 1929-1930 (part two). (Box 634, Folder 4)
    - Files of E.J. Marrin, Chief Clerk and/or Assistant Superintendent L.H. Jones, 1933-1941
      - General Correspondence, A-B, 1934-1941. (Box 635, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, B-C, 1935-1941. (Box 635, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence, C-E, 1933-1941. (Box 635, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, E-H, 1933-1941. (Box 635, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, H-I, 1934-1941. (Box 635, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, I-L, 1933-1941. (Box 636, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, M-N, 1933-1941. (Box 636, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence, N-R, 1934-1941. (Box 636, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, R-S, 1934-1941. (Box 636, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, S-W, 1933-1941. (Box 636, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, W, 1936-1941. (Box 637, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, Y, 1935-1940. (Box 637, Folder 2)
      - Camp 1, 1939-1941 (Sgt. E.H. Ward). (Box 638, Folder 1)
      - Camp 2, 1938-1941 (Sgt. A.T. Cocke). (Box 638, Folder 2)
      - Camp 3, 1938-1941 (Sgt. G.E. Bishop and E.T. Burnett). (Box 638, Folder 3)
      - Camp 4, 1936, 1938-1941 (Sgt. R.J. Garnett). (Box 638, Folder 4)
      - Camp 5, 1938-1941 (Sgt. J.C. Richardson). (Box 638, Folder 5)
      - Camp 6, 1938-1941 (Sgt. W.T. Reames, and C.L. Edwards). (Box 638, Folder 6)
      - Camp 7, 1938-1941 (Sgt. W.B. Davis and F.B. Bishop). (Box 638, Folder 7)
      - Camp 8, 1938-1941 (Sgt. L.E. Clouse). (Box 638, Folder 8)
      - Camp 9, 1938-1941 (Sgt. R.G. Holt). (Box 638, Folder 9)
      - Camp 10, 1938-1941 (Sgt. T.B. Harris). (Box 638, Folder 10)
      - Camp 11, 1938-1941 (Sgt. W.H. Wade). (Box 638, Folder 11)
      - Camp 12, 1938-1941 (Sgt. B.K. Spurrier). (Box 638, Folder 12)
      - Camp 13, 1938-1941 (Sgt. M.L. Royster). (Box 638, Folder 13)
      - Camp 14, 1938-1941 (Sgt. M.C. Russell). (Box 639, Folder 1)
      - Camp 15, 1938-1941 (Sgt. W.B. Moore). (Box 639, Folder 2)
      - Camp 16, 1938-1941 (Sgt. F.R. Hawkins). (Box 639, Folder 3)
      - Camp 17, 1938-1941 (Sgt. G.P. Bowman). (Box 639, Folder 4)
      - Camp 18, 1938-1941 (Sgt. G.E. Houston and R.R. O'Meara). (Box 639, Folder 5)
      - Camp 19, 1938-1941 (Sgt. Robert King). (Box 639, Folder 6)
      - Camp 20, 1938-1941 (Sgt. G.W. Earman). (Box 639, Folder 7)
      - Camp 21, 1938-1941 (Sgt. B.R. Jennell). (Box 639, Folder 8)
      - Camp 22, 1938-1941 (Sgt. L.D. Worley). (Box 639, Folder 9)
      - Camp 23, 1938-1941 (Sgt. O.R. Williams). (Box 639, Folder 10)
      - Camp 24, 1938-1941 (Sgt. W.W. Harvey). (Box 640, Folder 1)
      - Camp 25, 1938-1941 (Sgt. E.L. Carter and W.B. Davis). (Box 640, Folder 2)
      - Camp 26, 1938-1941 (Sgt. J.T. McCraw, R.R. O'Meara, R.L. Painter and E.O. Peed). (Box 640, Folder 3)
      - Camp 27, 1939-1941 (Sgt. C.T. Smith). (Box 640, Folder 4)
      - Camp 29, 1938-1941 (Sgt. F.B. Bishop, R.L. Painter and G.E. Houston). (Box 640, Folder 5)
      - Camp 30, 1938-1941 (Sgt. J.M. Peebles). (Box 640, Folder 6)
      - Camp 31, 1938-1941 (Sgt. D.P. Edwards). (Box 640, Folder 7)
      - Camp 32, 1938-1941 (Sgt. N.G. Doughtie). (Box 640, Folder 8)
  - Series V. Subseries D. Financial Records, 1906-1937. (Box 641-659., Volumes 188-204, 222, 255, 268-269, 272-274, 287.)
    This subseries is housed in 19 boxes and contains 24 volumes and includes: payrolls, inventories, requisitions, ration accounts and State Prisoners' Board Accounts. The Payroll records, 1916, 1918, 1922-1925, are arranged by month and by camp therein. The payroll lists the name of guard, days worked, rate and signature. The Inventories, 1908, 1913-1918, are arranged by year and camp therein. The inventories list the equipment, provisions, tools and implements, lights, stationery, clothing, fuel, tobacco, laundry, arms and ammunition, stable and miscellaneous items. The ration accounts, 1915-1916, are arranged by date and by camp therein and lists supplies received and used each month (food, etc.). The State Prisoners' Board Accounts, 1914-1917, are arranged by date and by camp therein. Each account list the name of prisoners (jailmen), locality sent from, race, offense, date received, date of release, number of days served, rate per day for keeping and amount.
    - Payroll, December 1916. (Box 641, Folder 1)
    - Payroll, May 1918. (Box 641, Folder 2)
    - Payroll, July 1918. (Box 641, Folder 3)
    - Payroll, August-September 1922. (Box 642, Folder 1)
    - Payroll, October-November 1922. (Box 642, Folder 2)
    - Payroll, December 1922-January 1923. (Box 642, Folder 3)
    - Payroll, February-March 1923. (Box 642, Folder 4)
    - Payroll, April 1923. (Box 642, Folder 5)
    - Payroll, January-February 1924. (Box 643, Folder 1)
    - Payroll, March-April 1924. (Box 643, Folder 2)
    - Payroll, May-June 1924. (Box 643, Folder 3)
    - Payroll, July-August 1924. (Box 643, Folder 4)
    - Payroll, September-October 1924. (Box 643, Folder 5)
    - Payroll, November-December 1924. (Box 644, Folder 1)
    - Payroll, January-February 1925. (Box 644, Folder 2)
    - Payroll, March-April 1925. (Box 644, Folder 3)
    - Payroll, May-June 1925. (Box 644, Folder 4)
    - Payroll, July-August 1925. (Box 644, Folder 5)
    - Payroll, September-October 1925. (Box 645, Folder 1)
    - Contingent Funds, November 1926 (part one). (Box 645, Folder 2)
    - Contingent Funds, November 1926 (part two). (Box 645, Folder 3)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1908. (Box 646, Folder 1)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1913 (part one). (Box 646, Folder 2)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1913 (part two). (Box 646, Folder 3)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1913 (part three). (Box 646, Folder 4)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1914 (part one). (Box 647, Folder 1)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1914 (part two). (Box 647, Folder 2)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1914 (part three). (Box 647, Folder 3)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1915 (part one). (Box 647, Folder 4)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1915 (part two). (Box 647, Folder 5)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1916 (part one). (Box 647, Folder 6)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1916 (part two). (Box 648, Folder 1)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1916 (part three). (Box 648, Folder 2)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1916 (part four). (Box 648, Folder 3)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1916 (part five). (Box 648, Folder 4)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1918 (part one). (Box 648, Folder 5)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1918 (part two). (Box 648, Folder 6)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1918 (part three). (Box 649, Folder 1)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1918 (part four). (Box 649, Folder 2)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, 1918 (part five). (Box 649, Folder 3)
    - Inventories, Camp Equipment, undated (Camp 28). (Box 649, Folder 4)
    - Requisitions, Camp 18, 1926-1927. (Box 650, Folder 1)
    - Requisitions, Camp 20, 1926-1928. (Box 650, Folder 1)
    - Requisitions, Camp 21, 1926-1928. (Box 650, Folder 1)
    - Requisitions, Camp 22, 1926-1928. (Box 650, Folder 1)
    - Requisitions, Camp 24, 1926-1928. (Box 650, Folder 2)
    - Requisitions, Camp 29, 1926-1927. (Box 650, Folder 2)
    - Requisitions, Camp 30, 1926-1928. (Box 650, Folder 3)
    - Requisitions, Camp 31, 1926-1928. (Box 650, Folder 3)
    - Requisitions, Camp 32, 1926-1928. (Box 650, Folder 3)
    - Contingent Expenses, Camp 1-16, June 1918. (Box 650, Folder 4)
    - Contingent Expenses, Camp 17-33, June 1918. (Box 650, Folder 5)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1914, 1916 (No. 1597, 1606, No. 2171-No. 2182, No. 2186-No. 2187, No. 2240-No. 2242, No. 2250-No. 2252). (Box 651, Folder 1)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1916 (No. 4981-No. 5024). (Box 651, Folder 2)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1916 (No. 5025-No. 5078). (Box 651, Folder 3)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1916 (No, 5079-No. 5084). (Box 651, Folder 4)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1916 (No. 5085-No. 5096). (Box 651, Folder 5)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1916 (No. 5097-No. 5113). (Box 652, Folder 1)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1916, 1919 (No. 5114-5115, 5260-5316). (Box 652, Folder 2)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1919 (No. 5317-5334. 5337-5359). (Box 652, Folder 3)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1920 (No. 9364-9394). (Box 652, Folder 4)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1920 (No. 9395-9416). (Box 652, Folder 5)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1920 (No. 9417-9422). (Box 652, Folder 6)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1920-1921 (No. 9423-9461). (Box 653, Folder 1)
    - Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1921 (No. 9462-9485, 9786-9787, 10714, 10721, 10736). (Box 653, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Bills and Cancelled Checks, 1916-1919, 1923. (Box 653, Folder 3)
    - Contingent Expenses, Camp 1-10, October 1913. (Box 653, Folder 4)
    - Contingent Expenses, Camp 14-15, February 1914. (Box 653, Folder 5)
    - Contingent Expenses, Camp 11-14, October 1916. (Box 653, Folder 6)
    - Contingent Expenses, 1917. (Box 653, Folder 7)
    - Contingent Expenses, Camp 1-15, April 1918. (Box 653, Folder 8)
    - Contingent Expenses, Camp 16-33, April 1918. (Box 653, Folder 9)
    - Contingent Expenses, Camp 1-16, May 1918. (Box 653, Folder 10)
    - Contingent Expenses, Camp 17-33, May 1918. (Box 654, Folder 1)
    - Expense Account, Camp 15 (Albemarle County), 1911-1913. (Box 654, Folder 2)
    - Guard and Convicts Transportation Certificate Book, 1915-1916 - Volume 204 (Box 654, Folder 3)
    - Transportation Certificates, 1915, 1916. (Box 654, Folder 4)
    - Transportation Certificates, 1917, 1918 and 1927. (Box 654, Folder 5)
    - Transportation Certificates, 1923. (Box 654, Folder 6)
    - Time and Pay Book, Camp 14, August 1917 to February 1920. (Box 654, Folder 7)
    - Statement of Invoices Paid, March 1937. (Box 654, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Prisoner Accounts, 1920-1921 (General and by Camp). (Box 654, Folder 9)
    - Ration Accounts, September 1916. (Box 655, Folder 1)
    - Ration Accounts, August 1916. (Box 655, Folder 2)
    - Ration Accounts, July 1916. (Box 655, Folder 3)
    - Ration Accounts, June 1916. (Box 655, Folder 4)
    - Ration Accounts, May 1916. (Box 655, Folder 5)
    - Ration Accounts, April 1916. (Box 655, Folder 6)
    - Ration Accounts, March 1916. (Box 655, Folder 7)
    - Ration Accounts, February 1916. (Box 655, Folder 8)
    - Ration Accounts, January 1916. (Box 655, Folder 9)
    - Ration Accounts, December 1915. (Box 655, Folder 10)
    - Ration Accounts, November 1915. (Box 655, Folder 11)
    - Ration Accounts, October 1915. (Box 655, Folder 12)
    - Ration Accounts, September 1915. (Box 655, Folder 13)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, August 1917. (Box 656, Folder 1)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, July 1917. (Box 656, Folder 2)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, June 1917. (Box 656, Folder 3)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, May 1917. (Box 656, Folder 4)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, April 1917. (Box 656, Folder 5)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, March 1917. (Box 656, Folder 6)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, February 1917. (Box 656, Folder 7)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, January 1917. (Box 656, Folder 8)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, December 1916. (Box 657, Folder 1)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, November 1916. (Box 657, Folder 2)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, October 1916. (Box 657, Folder 3)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, September 1916. (Box 657, Folder 4)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, August 1916. (Box 657, Folder 5)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, July 1916. (Box 657, Folder 6)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, June 1916. (Box 657, Folder 7)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, May 1916. (Box 657, Folder 8)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, April 1916. (Box 657, Folder 9)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, March 1916. (Box 657, Folder 10)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, February 1916. (Box 658, Folder 1)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, January 1916. (Box 658, Folder 2)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, December 1915. (Box 658, Folder 3)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, November 1915. (Box 658, Folder 4)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, October 1915. (Box 658, Folder 5)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, September 1915. (Box 658, Folder 6)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, August 1915. (Box 658, Folder 7)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, July 1915. (Box 658, Folder 8)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, June 1915. (Box 658, Folder 9)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, May 1915 (Box 658, Folder 10)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, April 1915. (Box 659, Folder 1)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, March 1915. (Box 659, Folder 2)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, February 1915. (Box 659, Folder 3)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, January 1915. (Box 659, Folder 4)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, December 1914. (Box 659, Folder 5)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, November 1914. (Box 659, Folder 6)
    - State Prisoners' Board Account, October 1914. (Box 659, Folder 7)
    - Lists of Employees of the State Convict Road Force, 1910. (Box 659, Folder 8)
    - Equipment and Cost of Maintenance, undated. (Box 659, Folder 9)
    - Account Book (Camps 1-14), 1909. (Volume 188)
    - Account Book, Camp 7, 1915-1923. (Volume 272)
    - Account Book, Camp 9, 1908-1915. (Volume 273)
    - Cash Book, October 1918 to September 1923. (Volume 255)
    - Disbursements, July 1915 to November 1916. (Volume 190)
    - Disbursements, December 1916 to January 1919. (Volume 191)
    - Disbursements, January 1919 to July 1921. (Volume 192)
    - Disbursements, March 1921 to February 1922. (Volume 193)
    - Disbursements, March 1922 to September 1923. (Volume 194)
    - Disbursements, October 1923 to February 1925. (Volume 195)
    - Disbursements, September 1930 to August 1932. (Volume 196)
    - Disbursements (Jail Camps), September 1932 to October 1933. (Volume 197)
    - Disbursements, November 1933 to [December] 1934. (Volume 198)
    - Disbursements, January 1935 to January 1936. (Volume 199)
    - Disbursements, February 1936 to February 1937. (Volume 200)
    - Journal, Unidentified SCRF Camp, April 1922 to April 1925. (Volume 287)
    - Ledger [list by name of Camp Sgts.], 1906-1909. (Volume 201)
    - Ledger, 1906-1921. (Volume 222)
    - Ledger, September 1921 to October 1922. (Volume 189)
    - Monthly Time Book, 1916-1917 and 1917-1918. (Volume 202)
    - Monthly Time Book (Jail/Stripemen), March to December 1923. (Volume 274)
    - Pay Book Stubs, 1919. (Volume 268)
    - Payments to Dr. M.H. Tridway for treatment of prisoners at Camp 6, April 1922 to May 1923. (Volume 203)
    - List of subscriptions to "The Golden Link", May-August 1891 (p. 215). (Volume 203)
- Series VI. State Convict Lime Grinding Board, 1914-1934, 1937 (bulk 1914-1922)., Extent: 12.10 cubic feet of records. (Box 660-686, Oversize Box 2 and one volume.)
  The State Convict Lime Grinding Board series is housed in 27 boxes (including five volumes), one oversize folder and contains one volume. It is arranged into four (4) subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Minutes; B. Correspondence; C. Financial Records; and D. Records from the Dept. of Agriculture and Commerce. These records include correspondence, minutes, orders, reports, photographs, vouchers, invoices, bills of lading, payrolls and financial records. This series documents the activities of the State Convict Lime Grinding Board.
  The State Convict Lime Grinding Board, comprised of the Governor, Superintendent and Commissioner of Agriculture, was created by the General Assembly in 1912. The Board was empowered to build facilities to grind limestone and to use convict labor. The Board was abolished by the state government reorganization act passed by the General Assembly in 1927 and its duties were transferred to the Board of Agriculture and Immigration.
  Additional information on the creation of the State Convict Lime Grinding Board may be found in the records of Governor William Hodges Mann (1910-1914), Governor Henry Carter Stuart (1914-1918) and Governor Westmoreland Davis (1918-1922).
  - Series VI. Subseries A: Minutes, 1914-1921, 1923. (Box 660.)
    This subseries contains one box (one folder and one volume) and is arranged chronologically. These records contain the minutes of the State Convict Lime Grinding Board from 1914 to 1921 and 1923. The board consisted of three members: Governor (chairman), Commissioner of Agriculture and Penitentiary Superintendent. The Board was created by the General Assembly in 1914 and supervised the employment of state penitentiary convicts at State Lime Grinding Plant No. 1 (Staunton) and State Lime Grinding Plant No. 2. (Irvington). The 1927 state government reorganization act abolished the Board and transferred its duties to the Board of Agriculture and Immigration (later renamed Dept. of Agriculture and Commerce. Information in these records includes: correspondence, awarding of contracts, approval of bills and financial information, construction of plants, installation of machinery, and facility improvements. The minutes give insight into the decision-making process and governance of the Stat Convict Lime Grinding Board. The minutes are typed and are not indexed.
    - State Lime Grinding Board, Minutes, 1914-1915 (volume) (Box 660)
    - State Lime Grinding Board, Minutes, 1916-1921, 1923. (Box 660, Folder 1)
  - Series VI. Subseries B: Correspondence, 1914-1925. (Box 661-680.)
    This subseries is housed in 20 boxes. The Correspondence subseries is further divided into: B.I. Construction of Plant No. 1, 1914-1915; B.II. Orders (both plants), 1915-1923; B.III. Secretary of State Lime Grinding Board, 1918-1925; B.IV. State Lime Grinding Plant No. 1, 1919-1922; B.V. State Lime Grinding Plant No. 2, 1917-1922; B.VI. Orders for State Lime Grinding Plant No. 2, 1917-1918; B.VII. Orders Shipped, 1917-1922, 1924; and B.VIII. Miscellaneous Records, 1916-1921.
    - Series VI.B.I. Construction of Plant No. 1, 1914-1915. (Box 661.)
      The Construction of Plant No. 1 records are housed in five folders. Correspondence are from the Governor's Office regarding site selection, rail access, purchase and installation of equipment and the construction of State Lime Grinding Plant No. 1 in Staunton, Virginia.
      - Correspondence, 1914. (Box 661, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1914. (Box 661, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1914. (Box 661, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, ca. 1914. (Box 661, Folder 4)
      - Maps and drawings showing proposed side track extension to State Lime Grinding Plant, Staunton, Va. (3 sheets), 1914. (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1915. (Box 661, Folder 5)
    - Series VI.B.II. Orders (both plants), 1915-1923. (Box 661-674.)
      The Orders (both plants), 1915-1923, are housed in 13 boxes. The orders are arranged by first letter of surname, then in reverse chronological order. The correspondence related to orders placed with the State Lime Convict Grinding Board.
      - VI.B.II.1. 1915-1919 (Box 661-665.)
        - Correspondence, A, 1916-1919. (Box 661, Folder 6)
        - Blueprints by Allis-Chalmers Mfg. Co., State Convict Lime Grinding Oyster Shell Plant, Irvington, Va., December 1916. (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, B, 1917-1919 (part one). (Box 661, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence, B, 1917-1919 (part two). (Box 662, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, B, 1917-1919 (part three). (Box 662, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, C, 1918. (Box 662, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, D, 1916, 1918. (Box 662, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, E, 1916-1919. (Box 662, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence, F, 1916-1919 (part one). (Box 662, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, F, 1916-1919 (part two). (Box 662, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence, G, 1915, 1918. (Box 662, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence, K, 1915-1916. (Box 663, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, L, 1915-1916. (Box 663, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, P, 1916-1919 (part one). (Box 663, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, P, 1916-1919 (part two). (Box 663, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, R, 1916-1919 (part one). (Box 663, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence, R, 1916-1919 (part two). (Box 663, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, S, 1915-1919 (part one). (Box 663, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence, S, 1915-1919 (part two). (Box 664, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, S, 1915-1919 (part three). (Box 664, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, S, 1915-1919 (part four). (Box 664, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, T, 1917-1919. (Box 664, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, U-V, 1916-1918. (Box 664, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence, W-Y, 1917-1919 (part one). (Box 664, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, W-Y, 1917-1919 (part two). (Box 665, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, W-Y, 1917-1919 (part three). (Box 665, Folder 2)
      - VI.B.II.2. 1919-1923 (Box 665-674.)
        - Correspondence, A, 1920-1922. (Box 665, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, A, 1919-1920 (part one). (Box 665, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, A, 1919-1920 (part two). (Box 665, Folder 5)